<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FUSEE 3D</title>
    <link>http://fusee3d.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FUSEE 3D</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://fusee3d.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First FUSEE App</title>
      <link>http://fusee3d.org/page/firstfuseeapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fusee3d.org/page/firstfuseeapp/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: Developing FUSEE Apps is currently only supported on Windows operating systems.
 After a successful FUSEE Installation you might want to create your first FUSEE App in Visual Studio Code.
Create a simple FUSEE App  Create a new empty directory somewhere on your hard-disk. This will contain your first FUSEE App. Name the directory MyFirstFuseeApp.
 Open the the directory in Visual Studio Code in one of the following ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install FUSEE</title>
      <link>http://fusee3d.org/page/install-fusee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fusee3d.org/page/install-fusee/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: Developing FUSEE Apps is currently only supported on Windows operating systems.
 Before following the FUSEE installation instructions on this page, make sure all Necessary Tools are installed.
Installation  Download the latest FUSEE Release from the FUSEE GitHub Repository.
 Copy or move the downloaded Fusee_v0.7.0.exe to a convenient place on your hard drive. This will become the home of your FUSEE installation.
   IMPORTANT: On some systems, the executable file is blocked and it may fail to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Necessary Tools</title>
      <link>http://fusee3d.org/page/necessary-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://fusee3d.org/page/necessary-tools/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: Developing FUSEE Apps is currently only supported on Windows operating systems.
 Prerequisites Before installing FUSEE, make sure the following software is installed.
Blender (optional) Create 3D models with the OpenSource 3D modelling Software Blender and use them as assets in your FUSEE application. The FUSEE installation will try to detect a Blender installation on your machine and will install the FUSEE Blender Add-on.
Install blender from https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>